
Question:

33. Steve would like to determine the relative salaries of three
coworkers using two facts. First, he knows that if Fred

is not the highest paid of the three, then Janice is. Sec-
ond, he knows that if Janice is not the lowest paid, then

Maggie is paid the most. Is it possible to determine the
relative salaries of Fred, Maggie, and Janice from what
Steve knows? If so, who is paid the most and who the
least? Explain your reasoning.



Answer:
     
    Steve's determination should be:

 Fred is the highest paid of the three.

 Maggie is paid less than Fred.

 Janice is  the lowest paid.

Explanation: 
 First fact was that if Fred is not the highest paid of the three, then Janice is.
now, Fred is the highest paid of the three and Janice is not. So, first fact remains true.

 
Second was that ,if Janice is not the lowest paid, then Maggie is paid the most.
now, as Janice is the lowest paid, so then Maggie is not paid the most. So, second fact remains true.


